{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Attic Renovation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62395/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62395,"taskName":"Attic - Remodel","taskDescription":"Remodel or Convert an Attic","xmTaskDescriptor":"Attic Renovation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"conversion, convert, attic, remodeling, remodel, renovate, renovation","textMessagingName":"Remod Attic","rolloverLongDesc":"Larger scale renovation, repairs \u0026 fix ups where multiple trades are involved. There are specific categories for additions, home theaters, kitchens, baths, basements \u0026 handicap accommodation. If project doesn't fit those categories, use this general category. Note that remodeling implies major work, in which walls are moved or rebuilt. For minor alterations, see specific categories such as handyman, painting, tile work or carpentry.","rolloverShortDesc":"Larger scale renovation, repairs \u0026 fix ups where multiple trades are involved","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel or Convert an Attic.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Attic Remodeling Contractors \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Attic Conversions","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Have a variety of small projects? How about hiring a ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"handyman?","bridgeTaskLinkId":15312,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Attic Remodeling","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Attic - Remodel","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Attic Renovation Project","urlName":"Attic-Remodel-Conversion","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Attic Remodeling \u0026 Conversion Contractors in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"conversion, convert, attic, remodeling, remodel, renovate, renovation","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8891,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62395/":{"taskOID":62395,"originalTaskOID":62395,"setID":8891,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502445,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":17575,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","answerDisplayText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17576,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel as part of home addition","answerDisplayText":"Remodel as part of home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17574,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4411,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4928,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional drawings (complete set of plans)","answerDisplayText":"Professional drawings (complete set of plans)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502445,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this remodel / renovation project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":17575,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","answerDisplayText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17576,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel as part of home addition","answerDisplayText":"Remodel as part of home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17574,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17575,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","answerDisplayText":"Reconfigure the current floor plan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17576,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel as part of home addition","answerDisplayText":"Remodel as part of home addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17574,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Remodel / update a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4411,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4928,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional drawings (complete set of plans)","answerDisplayText":"Professional drawings (complete set of plans)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4928,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional drawings (complete set of plans)","answerDisplayText":"Professional drawings (complete set of plans)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}